WEBMASTER

Managing web servers, sites and systems since 1999. I particularly enjoy inheriting older sites that need a bit of TLC (so don't we all?). Google Workspace Administrator for an 800 user Google Workspace since 2020. I am fluent in BASH, HTML, CSS and GAMADV. I can configure email domains to be DMARC compliant. Broderbund, Mattel Interactive, and Peet's Coffee are a few of the companies I've worked for. I am passionate about **Accessibility**.

EXPERIENCE

Webmaster bsc.coop August 2019-present

Berkeley Student Cooperative, Berkeley, CA Google Workspace/Drupal/MediaWiki/Apache/DMARC/SPF/DKIM

Webmaster peets.com August 2011-November 2019

Peet's Coffee, Emeryville, CA Microsoft ASP/IIS, Magento/Apache/Nginx

Freelance Web Developer, June 2009-August 2011

Various Web Development for Bay Area clients such as Swirl Interactive, Eleven Inc., AAA, Callaway Golf, Lennar Homes, Tuck School at Dartmouth, AARP, eBay, PayPal/BillMeLater and PG&E

Web Consultant: Wells Fargo, SF, December 2009–May 2010Consulted on solutions addressing the merger of the Wachovia and Wells Fargo intranets for the Wealth Management Marketing division

Digital Production Artist, Hamilton Partners, Healdsburg, CA April 2004–May 2009

Digital Prepress/Web Development for RadioShack's ZipZaps, Xmods, and VEX Robotics kits, Microsoft's Encarta brand, and HP's small and medium business printer division

Assistant Webmaster, Production Artist, Print and Web, Broderbund/Mattel Interactive/Riverdeep, Novato, CA March 1999–April 2004
Digital Prepress/Web Development for riverdeep.net, and the Creative Services intranet, Printmaster, Calendar Creator, Print Shop, Carmen Sandiego, The Oregon Trail, Reader Rabbit, and Destination Series

Digital Pre-Press, All-American Printing Services, Novato, CA November 1996–March 1999

Digital pre-press in a turn-key print facility

EDUCATION

DEQUE UNIVERSITY 2023

Accessibility Fundamentals - Disabilities, Guidelines, and Laws

O'REILLY SCHOOL OF TECHNOLOGY IN ASSOCIATION WITH THE UNIVERSITY OF ILLINOIS AT URBANA-CHAMPAIGN, 2011-2013

The C Programming Language, PHP, Java, Javascript

GRAPHIC ARTS INSTITUTE, SAN FRANCISCO, CA JUNE 1997-JUNE 1998

Advanced Pagination with QuarkXPress, Advanced Illustration with Illustrator, Advanced Editing with Photoshop

COLLEGE OF MARIN/INDIAN VALLEY COLLEGE, KENTFIELD/NOVATO, CA

English, English Composition, Critical Thinking

ENVIRONMENTS

Linux, Bash, Mac, Windows